bevmo.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy and Security Policies - BevMo!

Beverages & More, Inc. (hereinafter “BevMo!”, “Company”, “we” or ”us”) is committed to respecting your privacy and recognizing your need for appropriate protection and management of contact information you share with us (the phrase "contact information" means any information by which you can be contacted or personally identified, such as your name, mailing address, email address, home/work/mobile telephone number, etc.). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review, correct and opt out of our use of, the information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you in our stores and through our website and mobile application. By using our website, mobile application, or sharing your contact information with us, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Collecting Information About You**

There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product) when we ask you to provide certain contact information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, home/work/mobile telephone number, email address, credit card information, birth date and other information. We may also maintain a record of your product purchases.

Whether or not to provide such information is completely your choice. But if you choose not to provide the information we request, you may be unable to purchase products, or access certain services, offers and content on our website. In addition, we may need to contact you via phone, email, or mail to address questions or issues specific to your order, entry, etc., even if you have opted to not receive marketing communications from us.

In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any contact information about yourself. We may track the Internet domain address from which people visit us, other electronic markers and identifiers and other information about our site and mobile app traffic. We may analyze this data for preferences, trends, site usage statistics, and to recognize you. We may also receive usage data from your mobile phone or other device you use to access our website or our mobile application, including location data, which we may also combine with other information.

 **Using Information About You**

We use your contact information for analytical and marketing purposes, such as:

  1. •     confirming and tracking your order, subscription, or registration;
  2. •     analyzing preferences, trends, and statistics;
  3. •     informing you of our new products, services, and offers; and
  4. •     providing you with other information from and about BevMo!

We contact you only in ways compatible with your communications choices. To the extent necessary for such purposes, we take reasonable steps to make sure that your contact information is accurate, complete, current, and otherwise reliable.  
To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online or in our stores. We may also combine that information with publicly available information. We use that combined information to enhance and personalize the shopping experience of you and other customers, and to recognize our customers so that we can communicate with you directly about our products and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data analysis and management, promotional services, etc(“Service Providers”). We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. We also ask our Service Providers to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. Our systems do not recognize "Do Not Track" signals. We also provide you with additional tools to opt out of marketing from us or certain transfers of your information. You can learn about this in the "Opting Out of Marketing" section of this Privacy Policy.  
In certain instances we may disclose your contact information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to BevMo!, or to others. We may also disclose your contact information when we believe the law or legal process requires it.

 **Opting Out Of Marketing; Updating and Deleting Information About You**

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you would like to update or correct your email address, mailing address home/work/mobile phone number or other contact information with us please contact our Customer Service team at 1.877.77BEVMO.

You may also click the designated unsubscribe link at the bottom of all email advertisements to be removed from future email updates.

If you previously opted-in to receiving text messages and wish to opt out of receiving text messages, please reply “STOP” to any text message from us. Once you opt-out via text messageyou will receive confirmation, via text message, that you will no longer receive text message communication from BevMo!.

Please note that any requests to remove or update your contact information may take up to seven to ten business days.

 **Cookies**

When you visit our website, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We may also use cookies in emails that you receive from us. A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. A session cookie expires immediately when you end your session (i.e., close your browser). A persistent cookie stores information on the hard drive so when you end your session and return to the same website at a later date the cookie information is still available. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service when you visit our website. We also use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products, services and advertising to suit the personal interests of you and others, estimate our audience size, assist our online merchants to track visits to and sales at our website, and to process your order and/or analyze your visiting patterns.

Certain of our Service Providers may use cookies and collect information on our behalf. They are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Service Providers. In addition, we or certain of our Service Providers, in connection with the services that they provide to us, may work with third parties who may use cookies to collect information to tailor advertising for you on our website, and to assist in reminding us of who you are. If you would like to opt out of accepting cookies altogether, you can generally set your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. However, certain features of our website may not work if you delete or disable cookies.

 **Security**

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of information transmitted to us. To guard your information delivered to us electronically, our websites use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). SSL encrypts your credit card number, name, and address so only we are able to decode your information. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your contact information, to the extent permitted by law, we do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our website, and you do so at your own risk.

We urge you to keep any password that you establish with us in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also remember to log off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

 **Protecting Underage Persons**

BevMo! takes special care to protect the safety and privacy of persons under the age of 21. We do not permit anyone under the age of 21 to register with us. We also do not send email or text messaging correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 21.

 **Links to Third Party Websites**

Our website may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked websites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked websites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked website before disclosing any of your information on such website.

 **Policy Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy in whole or in part, we will post a revised policyon our website, as applicable. Those changes will go into effect on the effective date posted in the notice and at the end of the revised Privacy Policy. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our website and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our website or other services constitutes your acceptance of the practices described in the revised Privacy Policy.

 **Your Feedback**

To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, please give us your feedback. You can call us at 1.877.77BEVMO or contact Customer Service at <http://www.bevmo.com/contact-us/>.

Effective Date: September 15, 2017
